baydin.com 2010-12-23

# Baydin - Privacy Policy

**General Information** Baydin respects the privacy of visitors to our online sites. Any personal information gathered on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used in ways for which you have specifically consented. We will never sell or rent any personal information collected from you to any third party. We will take special care to protect the privacy and security of your information. All Personally Identified Information gathered on this website is in accordance with the Privacy Policy. This policy came into affect on the 16th June 2009.

**Privacy Contact Information** You can contact Baydin regarding privacy matters via our online form at info@baydin.com

**Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information** Baydin will only collect personally identifiable data, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, when it is voluntarily submitted to us at this website. This information will be collected through an online form or when you contact Baydin regarding any other matter. 

**Tracking Technologies**   
**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** This website also collects and uses information in aggregate form to track the total number of visitors to our site, the number of visitors to each page of our site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and other such technical information. This is technical information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. No personally identifiable information is available in this process and referred to as "non-personally identifiable information". We use this data to better target our marketing efforts. 

**Cookies** Our website uses a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a token that a server gives to your browser when you access a website. Cookies are capable of storing many types of data. Cookies help provide additional functionality to the site or to help us analyze site usage more accurately. For instance, our server may set a cookie that keeps you from having to enter a password more than once during a visit to one of our sites. In all cases in which cookies are used, the cookie will not collect personally identifiable information except with your explicit permission. We do not, however, use cookies to track the navigational habits of identified visitors. 

**Change of Privacy Policy** If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. 

**Access to Your Information** If you would like us to delete any information we have about you, we shall unless its part of a condition of using one of our services. You may request to have your information deleted once the agreement of the service is deemed nullified. We will respond to your request to access, update or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity. 

**Security** We take careful measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. The information collected is stored on secure servers behind Google’s firewall. Please refer to Google Docs [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) for further information. We only provide access to your personal information to Baydin employees. 

**Disclosure of Information** All Personally Identified Information gathered can be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrants, subpoenas or other governmental orders. 

**Children** We do not intentionally collect information from persons under the age of 16. 

**Third Party Links and Advertisement** As a convenience to our visitors, Baydin sites currently contain links to a number of sites that we believe may offer useful information. The privacy policies and procedures described here do not apply to those sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their data collection and distribution policies. We do not use third party advertising companies to provide advertisements or allow third party advertisers to track your browsing 

**Contact Baydin**   
You can contact Baydin regarding any matter via email at info@baydin.com.
